let questions = [

    {
        question: 'Who is considered to be the father of modern fantasy?',
        option1: 'J.K. Rowling',
        option2: 'J.R.R. Tolkien',
        option3: 'Ernist Hemingway',
        answer:2
    },

    {
        question: 'In Harry Potter the character Dobby is what sort of creature?',
        option1: 'House Elf',
        option2: 'Goblin',
        option3: 'Witch',
        answer:1
    },

    {
        question: 'In Game of Thrones what is the name of the highest quality steel in the series?',
        option1: 'Targaryen',
        option2: 'Adamantium',
        option3: 'Valyrian',
        answer:3
    },

    {
        question: 'Who pulled the sword from the stone?',
        option1: 'King Arthur',
        option2: 'Merlin',
        option3: 'Queen Maeve',
        answer:1
    },

    {
        question: 'Gandolf had the title of "the Grey" and what else?',
        option1: 'the Blue',
        option2: 'the Green',
        option3: 'the White',
        answer:3
    },

    {
        question: 'Where can you find Narnia?',
        option1: 'In the oven',
        option2: 'In a wardrobe',
        option3: 'On the moon',
        answer:2
    },

    {
        question: 'A minotaur is a mix between a human and what animal?',
        option1: 'Bull',
        option2: 'Horse',
        option3: 'Goat',
        answer:1
    },

    {
        question: 'What weapon does Gimli the dwarf prefer?',
        option1: 'Sword',
        option2: 'Axe',
        option3: 'Whip',
        answer:2
    },

    {
        question: 'The MadHater may invite you to what sort of party?',
        option1: 'Frat',
        option2: 'Tea',
        option3: 'New Year Eve',
        answer:2
    },

    {
        question: 'Who killed Dumbledore?',
        option1: 'Harry Potter',
        option2: 'Hagrid',
        option3: 'Snape',
        answer:3
    },
]